{
    "id": "95d94843dc1a4f6da7172592a819fd52",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He has been ill …………………… three months.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "since",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I haven’t played football ………………….. a long time.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "since",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "This cloth is inferior …………………. that.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "than",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Everybody should pray ………………….. God.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "for",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He wrote ………………….. me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "to",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Can you explain this ………………… me?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "with",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Are you still ………………….. the same address?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "in",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Send this letter …………………… my new address.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "to",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He goes …………………. school.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I am obliged ………………….. you for this good turn.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "to",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}